我们研究了许多惯性传感器。
We've studied a number of inertial sensors.
我们看到的第一个传感器是加速度计，它测量总量
The first sensor that we looked at was the accelerometer and that measures the total
加速身体。
acceleration of a body.
这种加速可能是由于作用在身体上的力或加速度可能是由于
That acceleration might be due to forces acting on the body or the acceleration might be due
重力作用于身体。
to gravity acting on the body.
如果作用在身体上的唯一力是重力，那么我们可以使用测量的加速度
If the only force acting on a body is gravity, then we can use the acceleration measured
在身体上确定相对于重力矢量的滚转角和俯仰角
on the body to determine the roll and pitch angles with respect to the gravity vector
或向下的方向。
or the downward direction.
我们研究了能够测量角速度分量的陀螺仪
We looked at gyroscopes which are able to measure components of the angular velocity
的身体。
of the body.
而且，我们研究了可以感应地球磁性成分的磁力计
And, we looked at magnetometers which can sense components of the Earth’s magnetic
相对于附着在物体上的坐标系的场。
field with respect to the coordinate frame attached to the body of the object.
我们可以结合加速度计和磁力计的信息来确定方向
We can combine information from accelerometers and magnetometers to determine the orientation
关于磁北的身体。
of the body with respect to magnetic north.
最早的惯性导航系统类型被称为万向节和
The earliest types of inertial navigation systems were referred to as gimballed and
它们是我在本讲座中很早就展示的非常大的乐器。
they are very large instruments that I showed very early on in this lecture.
它包含一个自由浮动的陀螺稳定平台，称为稳定元件
It contains a free floating gyro-stabilized platform referred to as the stable element
它在这里由坐标系I显示。
and it’s shown here by the coordinate frame I.
该平台通过万向节机构连接到车辆。
That platform is connected to the vehicle by a gimbal mechanism.
随着车辆的方向改变，车身框架附接到车辆
As the orientation of the vehicle changes, the body frame which is attached to the vehicle
变化，但惯性坐标系I在空间中保持固定。
changes, but the inertial coordinate frame I remains fixed in space.
因此，我们可以通过测量车辆的角度来确定车辆的方向
We can, therefore, determine the orientation of a vehicle by measuring the angles of the
惯性框架固定在空间和车身框架之间的万向节
gimbals between the inertial frame which is fixed in space and the body frame which is
附在车上。
attached to the vehicle.
加速度计安装在陀螺稳定平台上，因此可以测量加速度
The accelerometers are mounted on the gyro- stabilized platform, so they measure acceleration
在惯性框架中的车辆。
of the vehicle in the inertial frame.
但是如果我们想要，并且我们知道车辆相对于惯性的方向
But if we want to, and we know the orientation of the vehicle with respect to the inertial
框架，我们可以将加速度矢量旋转到车身框架。
frame, we can rotate the acceleration vector in to the vehicles body frame.
这是阿波罗宇宙飞船上使用的万向节惯性测量单元的示意图。
This is a schematic of the gimballed inertial measurement unit used on the Apollo spacecraft.
稳定元件在这里显示，它包含三个旋转陀螺仪并保持
The stable element is shown here and it contains three spinning gyroscopes and they maintain
该平台相对于恒星的方向不变。
the orientation of that platform constant with respect to the stars.
该平台还包含三个加速度计，XA，YA和ZA。
That platform also contains three accelerometers indicated here, XA, YA and ZA.
万向节机构有效地允许航天器围绕稳定平台旋转
The gimbal mechanism effectively allows the spacecraft to rotate about the stable platform
而万向节的角度是由今天标准的老式传感器测量的
and the gimbal angles are measured by rather old fashioned sensors by today’s standard
叫做解析器。
called resolvers.
今天，几乎所有惯性测量单元都使用所谓的捷联配置。
Today, almost all inertial measurement units use what’s called the strap-down configuration.
我们有车身框架B连接到车辆，加速度计和陀螺仪测量
We have a body frame B attached to the vehicle and the accelerometers and gyroscopes measure
沿着每个车身框架轴和陀螺仪的加速度测量角度
acceleration along each of the body frame axis and the gyroscopes measure the angular
关于每个车身框架坐标轴的速度分量。
velocity components about each of the body frame coordinate axes.
随着车辆方向的改变，车身框架B也发生变化，我们测量角速度
As the vehicle orientation changes, so does the body frame B, we measure the angular velocity
在坐标系B中，我们将其随时间积分以确定方向
in the coordinate frame B and we integrate that over time to determine the orientation
车辆
of the vehicle.
一旦我们知道车身在车身框架中的方向，我们就可以将其旋转回来
Once we know the orientation of the vehicle in the body frame, we can rotate it back to
惯性框架确定我们相对于恒星的加速度。
the inertial frame to determine our acceleration with respect to the stars.